<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Astana\'s Sightseeings</string>
    <integer-array name="arrOfPIds">
        <item>0</item>
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>6</item>
        <item>7</item>
        <item>8</item>
        <item>9</item>
        <item>10</item>
        <item>11</item>
        <item>12</item>
    </integer-array>

    <string-array name="arrOfPNames">
        <item>Hazrat Sultan</item>
        <item>Nur Astana Mosque</item>
        <item>Khan Shatyr</item>
        <item>MEGA Astana</item>
        <item>Asia Park</item>
        <item>Astana Opera</item>
        <item>Baiterek Tower</item>
        <item>Duman</item>
        <item>Palace of Peace and Reconciliation</item>
        <item>National Museum</item>
        <item>Ice Palace Alau</item>
        <item>Keruen</item>
        <item>Astana Arena</item>
    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="arrOfPPics_main">
        <item>@drawable/hazret_sultan_pic</item>
        <item>@drawable/nur_astana_pic</item>
        <item>@drawable/khan_shatyr_pic</item>
        <item>@drawable/mega_astana</item>
        <item>@drawable/asia_park</item>
        <item>@drawable/astana_opera</item>
        <item>@drawable/baiterek_monument</item>
        <item>@drawable/duman_astana</item>
        <item>@drawable/piramida_astana</item>
        <item>@drawable/muzei_astana</item>
        <item>@drawable/alau_astana</item>
        <item>@drawable/keruen_astana</item>
        <item>@drawable/astana_arena</item>
    </integer-array>


    <string-array name="arrOfPHistories">
        <item>
            Hazrat Sultan - Mosque in Astana, the second largest mosque in Central Asia after
            the mosque in Turkmenistan \"Spirituality of Turkmenbashi.\"; It can accommodate
            five thousand worshipers, and on holidays - up to 10 thousand people. Area
            throughout the Hazrat Sultan Mosque is over 13 hectares and construction area of
            17,700 square metrov.6 July 2012 at 12:30 opening of mosque \"Hazrat Sultan\".
        </item>
        <item>
            \"Nur Astana\"; mosque - mosque height of 63 m and is 6.7 hectares, and the total
            area is 3930 square meters. meters. The opening took place on March 22, 2005.
            Human Capacity 10,000.
        </item>
        <item>
            \"Khan Shatyr\"; - a major shopping and entertainment. Opened July 6, 2010. The
            total area of Khan Shatyr - 127 thousand square meters. The room housed retail
            trade and entertainment complexes. Including a supermarket, a family park, cafes
            and restaurants, cinemas, sports facilities, a water park with an artificial beach and
            swimming pools with wave effect, service and office space, parking for 700 cars
            and more..
        </item>
        <item>
            MEGA Astana - a major shopping and entertainment center. The opening of the
            shopping center on 25 October 2007. The total area of the shopping center is 34
            500 m², and the commercial area of 22,640 m². In it is located 87 boutiques,
            hypermarket area of 2700 m², a hypermarket of toys and children\'s products,
            children\'s amusement park, a 6-screen cinema multiplex, a food court for 360 beds,
            9 cafés and restaurants. Car parking is available in the center of 510 seats..
        </item>
        <item>
            Asia Park- a large shopping and entertainment center. The opening of the shopping
            center on 17 December 2009. It is located supermarket \"Alma\";
            Film Centre \"Arman 3D\", family entertainment center «Baby Park», a restaurant
            overlooking the left bank of the «Sky Bar», a fitness club «Fitness First»,
            children\'s store, \"Golden Key\";.
        </item>
        <item>
            The operator Astana National Academic Theatre of Opera and Ballet. The opening
            took place on June 21, 2013. The theater is situated on the site of almost 9 hectares.
            The area of the building is 64 thousand square meters. Of these, about 3000 square
            meters occupies a scenic area.
        </item>
        <item>
            Baiterek Tower - Height of buildings is 97 meters with the ball, crowning the
            construction - 105 meters. The diameter of the ball 22 meters. The monument was
            built on the initiative of President Nursultan Nazarbayev, a transfer symbol of the
            capital from Almaty to Astana in 1997. The center installed a wooden globe
            autographed by representatives of 17 world religions, symbolizing the unity of all
            religions. The opening took place on August 30, 2002..
        </item>
        <item>
            Duman - Oceanarium \"Duman\"; entertainment center today is the first and so far
            the only one in the CIS. This - the only aquarium in the world, located on the ocean
            in the distance of over 3000 km. The volume of water in the aquarium Kazakh - 3
            million liters. For its creation were specially imported 120 tons of sea salt.
            The aquarium is home to over 2000 species of marine life, marine life from
            different parts of the world. It is located a souvenir shop, café, zoo -ekzotarium
            animatronics theater \"Jungle\". The opening took place in May 2003.
        </item>
        <item>
            Palace of Peace and Reconciliation - the pyramid, created specifically for \"the
            Congress of Leaders of World and Traditional Religions\"; Pyramid - center of
            religion and religious tolerance. It holds a concert hall for 1500 seats. Pyramid has
            become a symbol of unity of different religions, ethnicities and cultures, openness
            of the people and government worldwide. Pyramids area of ​​28 thousand square
            meters,;\"Palace of Peace and Accord\"; - It is equipped with modern equipment
            meeting rooms and exhibition areas, art galleries, presentation systems, and more.
            Opened September 1, 2006
        </item>
        <item>
            National Museum - National Museum of the Republic of Kazakhstan-opened July
            2, 2014. The museum was created as a result of the state program; \"Cultural
            Heritage\". It is the largest museum in the country. The total land area of 9.9
            hectares, a building area of 74,000 square meters, the exhibition area of 14,095
            square meters.
        </item>
        <item>
            Ice Palace \"Alau\"; - an indoor skating rink in Astana, Kazakhstan. Sports complex
            for the organization of competitions in speed skating and the organization of
            training for a mini-hockey, ice hockey, short track, curling, figure skating. Ice
            Arena consists of a 400-meter ice track with stands for 7,500 seats. It opened in
            2011.
        </item>
        <item>
            Keruen - a large shopping and entertainment center. The opening of the shopping center on July 15,
            2009. The total area of the shopping center is 58,000 square meters. In it there are shops, a
            hypermarket, a 7-screen cinema, cafes and restaurants. Car parking center is designed for 450 seats.
        </item>
        <item>
            Astana Arena - the stadium can accommodate 30,000 spectators. The stadium
            was originally, as in the official opening day, called Kazhymukan Stadium in
            honor of the famous wrestler Kazhymukan Munaitpasov. Later, the stadium has
            got its present name Astana Arena. Stadium, primarily focused on football, but can
            easily be adapted for other sports events, including the favorite sports in the
            country - wrestling, judo and boxing. Opened July 3rd, 2009. Sometimes you can
            enjoy a concert conducted by stars from different countries.
        </item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="arrOfPLats">
        <item>51.125488</item>
        <item>51.126582</item>
        <item>51.132539</item>
        <item>51.145503</item>
        <item>51.128233</item>
        <item>51.135319</item>
        <item>51.128300</item>
        <item>51.149000</item>
        <item>51.123135</item>
        <item>51.118491</item>
        <item>51.104892</item>
        <item>51.128128</item>
        <item>51.108224</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="arrOfPLons">
        <item>71.471935</item>
        <item>71.415737</item>
        <item>71.403822</item>
        <item>71.413648</item>
        <item>71.411798</item>
        <item>71.410650</item>
        <item>71.430500</item>
        <item>71.415489</item>
        <item>71.463532</item>
        <item>71.469652</item>
        <item>71.405066</item>
        <item>71.425365</item>
        <item>71.402636</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="arrOfPAddr">
        <item>Tauelsizdik Ave, 48, Аstana</item>
        <item>Kabanbay Batyr st, 36.</item>
        <item>Turan ave 37</item>
        <item>Korgalzhyn Rd. 1</item>
        <item>Kabanbay Batyr ave, 21</item>
        <item>Kunaev St 1</item>
        <item>Levoberezhe, 1</item>
        <item>Korgalzhynskoe Rd.</item>
        <item>Tauelsizdik ave, 57</item>
        <item>Tauelsizdik ave, 54</item>
        <item>Kabanbay Batyr ave 47</item>
        <item>Dostyk St, 9</item>
        <item>Turan Ave, 48</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="arrOfPPhoneAddr">
        <item>+7 7172 42 24 55, +7 7172 42 41 77</item>
        <item>8 (7172) 44-58-48, 44-61-65 </item>
        <item>+7(7172) 574-941, -942.</item>
        <item>8 (717) 279 0990</item>
        <item>8 (7172) 97 87 67</item>
        <item>+7 7172 709 600; +7 7172 709 612</item>
        <item>+7 (7172) 44 64 72</item>
        <item>8 (717) 279 1500</item>
        <item>8 (717) 274 4744</item>
        <item>8 (717) 291 9035</item>
        <item>+7 (7172) 706-722, 706-802</item>
        <item> +7 (7172) 79 55 20, 79 55 22</item>
        <item>8 (717) 270 2662</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="arrOfPWebAddr">
        <item>www.muslim.kz</item>
        <item>nurastana-05@mail.ru</item>
        <item>None</item>
        <item>None</item>
        <item>None</item>
        <item>None</item>
        <item>None</item>
        <item>None</item>
        <item>None</item>
        <item>None</item>
        <item>None</item>
        <item>None</item>
        <item>None</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="arrOfPHrs">
        <item>10.00-18.00</item>
        <item>10.00-18.00</item>
        <item>10.00-22.00</item>
        <item>10.00-22.00</item>
        <item>10.00-22.00</item>
        <item>10.00-18.45</item>
        <item>10.00-21.00</item>
        <item>10.30-20.30</item>
        <item>10.00-18.00</item>
        <item>10.00-18.00</item>
        <item>9.00-23.00</item>
        <item>10.00-22.00</item>
        <item>09:30-19:00</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="Photo">photos</string>
    <string name="PhotoLabel">Picture</string>
    <string name="HistoryLabel">History</string>
    <string name="LocationLabel">Location</string>
    <string name="Contacts">Contacts</string>
    <string name="PlaceName">PlaceName</string>
</resources>
